Grand Tutor,
المعلم الكبير ،
the file you asked for has arrived.
وصل الملف الذي طلبته.
Grand Tutor.
المعلم الكبير.
Lord Ning,
اللورد نينغ ،
Grand Tutor,
المعلم الكبير ،
I didn't expect that you're good at weapons.
لم أكن أتوقع أنك جيد في الأسلحة.
First, Li An,
أولا ، لي آن ،
then Ning Yi,
ثم نينغ يي ،
They all had a grudge against Fusu.
كان لديهم جميعًا ضغينة ضد فوسو.
Besides,
بجانب،
the way to die is almost the same.
طريق الموت هو نفسه تقريبا.
A bunch of losers,
حفنة من الخاسرين ،
Fusu escaped from prison.
هرب فوسو من السجن.
I'm sure
أنا متأكد
Fusu is the murderer.
فوسو هو القاتل.
There's not even a single fish in Daqin's prison,
لا يوجد حتى سمكة واحدة في سجن داقين ،
Lin Weixu,
لين ويكسو ،
Is this the result of your promise?
هل هذه نتيجة وعدك؟
If Your Majesty wants to punish me,
إذا أراد جلالة الملك أن يعاقبني ،
just give the order.
فقط أعط الطلب.
You.
أنت.
The murderer of Nanzhao has not been determined and the spy of Beiqi has not been caught,
لم يتم تحديد قاتل Nanzhao ولم يتم القبض على جاسوس Beiqi ،
why are you holding on to a merman?
لماذا تتمسك بحوري بحر؟
At this point,
عند هذه النقطة،
you still have to defend him.
لا يزال عليك الدفاع عنه.
I'm just talking about the matter.
أنا أتحدث فقط عن الأمر.
As for Fusu,
أما فوسو
I will capture him personally.
سوف ألتقطه شخصيا.
Give everyone an explanation.
قدم شرحا للجميع.
Okay
تمام
If I can't catch you back, you don't have to be a State Preceptor.
إذا لم أتمكن من إعادتك ، فلا داعي لأن تكون مستشار دولة.
Your Excellency,
امتيازك،
have some fruit.
بعض الفاكهة.
We have news about Fusu's movements.
لدينا أخبار عن تحركات فوسو.
Your Excellency,
امتيازك،
Fusu is going to commit a crime now.
فوسو سوف يرتكب جريمة الآن.
Walls have ears.
الجدران لها آذان.
What are you afraid of? I was ordered to investigate.
من ماذا انت خائف؟  لقد أُمرت بالتحقيق.
Hurry up!
أسرع - بسرعة!
Grand Tutor didn't attend the morning court before,
المعلم الكبير لم يحضر محكمة الصباح من قبل
but now he refuses to show up.
لكنه الآن يرفض الحضور.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Grand Tutor has been working day and night on the case of Beiqi spies,
Grand Tutor يعمل ليل نهار في قضية جواسيس Beiqi ،
please wait a bit longer.
من فضلك انتظر قليلا.
Junior Sister.
أخت صغيرة.
Why do you look so pale?
لماذا تبدين شاحبة جدا؟
You don't look much better.
أنت لا تبدو أفضل بكثير.
I was attacked by that merman
لقد هاجمني ذلك الحوري
Fu Su
فو سو
I must have provoked him before.
لا بد أنني استفزته من قبل.
That's why he retaliated against me.
لهذا انتقم ضدي.
Unfortunately,
للأسف،
I'm not as strong as him.
أنا لست قويا مثله.
Or did he run away?
أم أنه هرب؟